Jim Nowak. I got a lot of experience here at Phil's,
and go back all the way to Phil. And when Phil
sold, I was concerned because he had been such a great
person to work with. Never realized what a treat it would be once
Eddie purchased it. Eddie and young Eddie.
After Phil had left, came a time where I needed some car repair.
First impression of Ed, his son, was such that
I was confident that I would be well served, and that was nothing
but true. I've known him for several years now, and
he's always been there when we've needed him.
Went through a situation where I had a very bad
car accident, where I actually totaled both of our
cars. It was going to be an antsy thing with the insurance company.
Eddie took the bull by the horns, brought us in, talked to me like I was
his dad, giving me great advice. Went above and beyond like
he always did. And for all the time that I've known him,
we're not a client and an automobile repair guy, we're
family. He treats my wife like royalty.
If I ever go first, and she's left by herself, man, I know
she'll be in good hands. Eddie's always impressed me with how
thorough
and how accommodating. He can go on tours, put an
extra hour down. He helped us through our most dire of times
with the car accident. And this young man, he gets
better looking by the day.
When I had the accident, I was telling him then, I was fearful of getting back in
the car. And they diagnosed that episode as a form
of PTSD. And I want to say that the only reason I was able to
get back in the car was because of Ed, and they helped me get
through this whole thing.